ANA PINEDA

◆ ENABLEMENT PROGRAM MANAGER ◆

anapineda12@icloud.com ◆

www.linkedin.com/in/anamichellepineda



+949 556 739

PROFILE

Highly organized Sales Manager with the ability to multi-task in a fast-paced work environment.

Experienced in creating mutually beneficial relationships with clients through constant customer service ensuring a positive experience promoting repeat business and the achievement of personal and professional goals.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Executive Meeting Manager AC Hotel Irvine - Marriott Oct 2018 - Present

- Prospect for new corporate group business
- Establish and maintained a relationship with new and recurring clients
- Negotiate room rates to increase company profits
- Maintain and update all knowledge on industry trends
- Coordinate travel itineraries, meeting plans and reservations
- Manage payments and billing

Catering and Events Manager Hotel Paseo, Autograph Collection by Marriott Dec 2017 - Oct 2018

- As part of the opening team, I set up the catering and banquets menus, standard operating procedures, diagrams, software, vendors, designs, and more.
- Developed marketing strategies to increase awareness of hotel opening as the first hotel to be opened in the Palm Desert area in a decade.
- Established a relationship with local groups, associations, businesses and hotels to determine trends in the market to be able to maximize sales while managing revenue
- Detailed and serviced all hotel events working with an on-site third-party restaurant
- Researched and set up agreements with outside vendors for event-related services

Event Coordinator Anaheim Marriott Suites Marriott Mar 2016 - Dec 2017

- Point of contact for signed clients with the primary objective of up-selling through supportive customer service to achieve department revenue goals
- Conduct recurring banquet order meetings with department leaders
- Manage company income by ensuring timely and complete payment from clients.
- Design and create social packages to assist the sales team with potential clients

FUN FACTS

- I enjoy playing Sudoku every day
- In 2005 I lived in the Czech Republic as an exchange student
- Growing up I spoke English at home and Spanish in the outside world.
- Currently enrolled in a Computer
 Programming Boot Camp. I have the dream
 of learning to develop programs and
 applications.

EDUCATION

2019 - current (June 2020) Full Stack Software Developer UCLA Extension

2010 - 2014

Bachelor of Science, Major in Hotel Management

CESSA Universidad - Mexico City Graduated with Academic Merit

RELEVANT QUALIFICATIONS

- Extremely detail-oriented
- Prioritize efficient and effective communication with clients and team members to maximize clarity
- Problem-solving